hypefeeds.com 2018-02-12

# Privacy Policy | Hype Feeds

Privacy Policy  
HypeFeeds.com is committed to protecting your privacy. HypeFeeds.com currently collects no personal information about who visits our site. HypeFeeds.com uses a hit service that shows information such as which internet service visitors are using, their screen resolutions, browser types, etc. but in no way does this reveal the name, email address, or any specific information whatsoever about the site’s visitors.

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements:

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

Will HypeFeeds.com disclose collected information to outside parties?

HypeFeeds.com may eventually disclose the aforementioned GENERAL information about visitors – information that does NOT identify who you are. We may disclose answers to questions such as: during what time periods do we receive the most visitors, what is the most common browser version of our visitors, what are the most popular internet services our visitors use, etc. We will never release contact details of any registered users of our website. The last thing we want is “spam” reaching our visitors.

Your Consent:

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by HypeFeeds.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. But, now and forever we put your privacy first before any other concerns. We will never sell lists of email addresses from this site. We respect the privacy of our visitors.
